

DONARD AZURA

MECHANICAL ENGINEER DATA ANALYST



FACEBOOK /engr.donardazura



Github /Donard20



Linkedin /engrnard

% +639166257204

Muzon,SCJDM, Bulacan

SKILLS

SPECIALITIES

Data Manipulation

Data Visualization

Data Cleaning

Dashboard

ETL

TOOLS

Big Query SQL

Power BI

Goog Data Studio

Python

Excel

Word

REFERENCE

MIKE ALLAN NILLO / Analyst

Accenture

nilloallan@gmail.com

JANA ZEPEDA / BI Engineer

Uploan PH

© 09273216246

INTERESTING / CURRENT STUDY

HTML5 CSS ReactJS NodeJS

JavaScript

Git

Xcode

PostgreSQL

Swift Objective-C Data Algorithm Heroku

PROFILE INFO

Driven and detail-oriented Mechanical Engineer with 3 years of experience with the 3D design and fabrication of automotive parts. Troubleshooting skills, problem-solving, and analytical thinking skills. Acquired skills in Power BI and GDS for Data Visualization. Data Manipulation using SQL and basic Python.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYST COHORT 5

Eskwelabs

Feb 2022 - April 2022

- Data Cleaning
- Data Visualization
- Created Mock up Website
- Created Mock up ATS (Applicant Tracker System)
- Created Sentiment Analysis for Company
- Interpret Datasets

DESIGN ENGINEER

Nikki Manufacturing Inc., 2019-Present

- Design, model, and test prototypes for products.
- Conduct research and create design proposals for projects.
- Establish design briefs.
- Create concepts, performance, and production criteria.
- Identify and select materials needed for production.

ENGINEER

Myrex Pharma Manuf. 2017-2019

- Read and interpret blueprints in order to remove, layout, and install temperature control systems
- Practices to independently organize and schedule out own work.
- Learns to test and replace all safety devices on boilers to insure proper function.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Chicken Deli 2010-2012

- Responsible from file checking, minor editing, color correction, lay-outing and final output.
- Involved in designing team for future designs.

EDUCATION

2012-2017

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Dr. Yanga's Colleges Inc.,

MacArthur Highway, Bocaue, Bulacan

2008-2010

MULTIMEDIA ARTS | Asian Academy of Business and Computers 139 Maginhawa St., Brgy. Sikatuna Village, Q.C. Tel No: 436-0255

TAGALOG ENGLISH JAPANESE